Inventory of the Oscar Stonorov papers, 1912-1978 (bulk 1929-1970)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Series V. Subject Files, 1912-1971
  - Sub-series 1. General Files, 1912-1970
    - Papers and Reports, 1933-1967 (Box 43-44)
    - Photographs- Andre Lucrat Hotel, undated (Box 45)
    - Photographs- Buildings by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1912-1951 and undated (Box 44-45)
    - Photographs- Cornu, Andre, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Photographs- Dunn, James C., undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Photographs- Sculptures, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Photographs- Thom McAn Store, undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Photographs- Unidentified Negatives, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Photographs- Unidentified Photographs, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Photographs- Valley Forge Hospital, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Photographs- Wright, Frank Lloyd, undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Zi Club Model, undated (Box 54)
    - Publications, 1932-1962 (Box 46-47)
    - Research on Aging, 1959-1964 (Box 47-48)
    - Reuther, Walter, 1950-1970 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Sub-series 2. Newspaper Clippings, 1933-1971
    Contains newspaper clippings on various subjects, people, and projects by Stonorov.
    - Apartment Buildings by Oscar Stonorov, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - "The Bathers" Fountain, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Bronze Sculpture for Stonorov and Haw Firm, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - "The Builder" Bronze Statue, 1953-1954 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Bullitt Clippings, 1943 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Carl Mackley Houses (Hosiery Workers Apartments), 1933-1934 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - City Planning Clippings, 1948-1961 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Defense Housing Clippings, 1942 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Gimbels Store, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - House Designs by Stonorov, 1947-1956 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Mayfair Site, 1941 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1934-1969 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Oak Lane Park/ Hopkinson House, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Philadelphia Sports Stadium, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Walter Reuther, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Walter Reuther, Death of, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 17-18)
    - Solar House Clippings, 1947 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Solidarity House, 1951-1954 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Statues in Washington DC, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Steel Frame House, 1935-1947 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Tuscan Girl Fountain, 1965-1971 (Box 50, Folder 5-6)
    - University of Connecticut Law School, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1938-1951 (Box 50, Folder 8-9)
- Series VI. Biographical Materials, 1933-1978
  - Articles about Stonorov, 1943-1978 (Box 50)
  - Awards and Certificates, 1948-1972 (Box 51, Folder 1-7)
  - Death of Stonorov, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 8-11)
  - Exhibit on Stonorov, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Marriage of Oscar Stonorov, undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Memberships, 1933-1941 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Memorial Service Notes, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 15-17)
  - Personal Data, undated (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Photographs of Stonorov, undated (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Registration, 1935-1942 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Additional Container Lists
  The American Heritage Center is in the process of converting its older container lists to a more accessible format. This link is to an older version of a container list.
  - Link to Accessioning Worksheet (PDF)